noipfraud.com 2018-12-24

# NoIpFraud

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING ANY PART OF THE WEBSITE.

### I. OVERVIEW

NoIPFraud.com (the “Company”) recognizes and respects the privacy of users of this subscription Website. The following privacy policy, as modified from time to time by us as described below (the “Policy”), tells you about the information that the Company collects through the Website, how we use that information and how you can opt out of certain uses of information we may collect. If you access the Website (“NoIPFraud.com”) you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.

### II. EFFECTIVE AND UPDATES

This Privacy Policy is effective at 8:00 a.m. on Oct 1, 2011. The Company reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new effective date in the first sentence of this paragraph. The Company will not notify its Website visitors or customers of any such changes by e-mail or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit this Website so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications. Please note that this Policy applies to all information collected online by the Company.

### III. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you, specifically your name, postal delivery address, e-mail address, payment method (e.g., credit card or debit card) and telephone number, as well as other information when such information is combined with your personal information.

When you register or re-register at our Web site, we ask you to supply us and our payment processing partner with personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts. For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you. We use this personal information to process your registration, your subscriptions and your payments, and to communicate with you on these and other topics. We also use your e-mail address to send you newsletters, as well as messages about NoIPFraud.com special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your site activity, payment history and correspondence as well as any other related activity. We use this information for such purposes as providing recommendations on tools you may find useful, personalizing the site to better reflect particular interests, tracking your level of activity, helping us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise enhancing our service offering for our customers. We also provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We may also disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, site habits, commentary, reviews and other non-personal information about customers.

While using the NoIPFraud.com service and Web site, you will have opportunities to post reviews or other personal information in forums. Please understand that when you post such information, it is made public and is not subject to this policy.

### IV. VIEWING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the personal information you provide to us relating to your account. If you want to update your contact information please submit a support request with new account details to support@noipfraud.com.your payment method, you should do so by visiting the Your Account section of our Web site.

### V. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY

As you browse the NoIPFraud.com site, cookies may placed on your computer’s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.) In general, cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you may not be able to use particular services on the site.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how our users interact with our site and to otherwise help us efficiently operate and monitor our site and service. These technologies, show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our site and our service.

### VI. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as otherwise disclosed to you, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the personal information in advance and giving you an opportunity to prevent your personal information from being shared.

We use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our Web pages, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze and enhance data, including customers’ interaction with our site, and process consumer surveys. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them.

In addition, we may offer joint promotions or programs that, in order for participation, will require personal information be shared with third parties. In such instances, you will be provided with notice of the sharing prior to your decision to participate.

NoIPFraud.com also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety. In the event that NoIPFraud.com is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction provided that such third party continues to honor our privacy policy.

### VII. SECURITY

NoIPFraud.com takes information security very seriously and uses reasonable administrative, technical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. For example, we encrypt the personal information that you send to us through the registration and sign up process.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access your NoIPFraud.com account. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to the NoIPFraud.com Web site. You are solely responsible for maintaining secure login and password of the noipfraud client application. Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using this Web site, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

### VIII. CONTACT

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please email support@NoIPFraud.com.

Our address is PB Services LLC , 340 S LEMON AVE #8486, WALNUT, CA 91789, Attention: NoIPFraud.com Counsel.

\- top -
